<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Software engineering and reverse</title>
    <link>https://example.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Software engineering and reverse</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Killing a process started by IntelliJ Using Unlogged SDK</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/process-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/process-killer/</guid>
      <description>ps aux | grep java | grep unlogged-sdk- | grep -v grep | awk &amp;#39;{print $2}&amp;#39; | xargs kill -9 This is a command that can be used to identify and terminate Java processes that are using the UnLogged SDK library in Linux. Here&amp;rsquo;s an explanation of each part of the command:&#xA;ps aux: This command lists all currently running processes on the system, along with their process ID (PID), user ID, CPU usage, memory usage, and other relevant information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lombok works</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/how-lombok-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/how-lombok-works/</guid>
      <description>Introduction # Project Lombok is a java library that automatically plugs into your editor and build tools, spicing up your java.&#xA;Never write another getter or equals method again, with one annotation your class has a fully featured builder, Automate your logging variables, and much more. This post is not a guide to use lombok, you can find plenty of them with a search. This post is about how the lombok works internally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reserving Ids ahead of time</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/reserving-ids-ahead-of-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/reserving-ids-ahead-of-time/</guid>
      <description>Reserving entity IDs ahead of time can address a bunch of issues in software development and system design, particularly in distributed systems, databases, and applications requiring high concurrency or real-time processing. Here are some of the key benefits and problems that this approach can solve:&#xA;Avoiding Collisions and Ensuring Uniqueness In distributed systems where different nodes generate IDs independently, reserving IDs in batches can prevent collisions. Each node or service can reserve a block of IDs and use them without needing to coordinate with others in real time, ensuring uniqueness across the system.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
